<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tags on blog.raidsrc.me</title>
    <link>https://blog.raidsrc.me/tags/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tags on blog.raidsrc.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.raidsrc.me/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bye for Now</title>
      <link>https://blog.raidsrc.me/posts/bye-for-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 11:29:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.raidsrc.me/posts/bye-for-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Back at school. I made it into the UC Davis Jazz Ensembles despite completely missing auditions. But the band director has heard me play before, so at the very least he knows I&amp;rsquo;m not absolute garbage. Anyway, this means I&amp;rsquo;ve got to go to in-person rehearsals. We&amp;rsquo;ve got a concert coming up at the end of the quarter. And I&amp;rsquo;m rusty as hell at jazz drumming. Plus I got a cut on my left thumb from a super sharp scalpel and the bandage makes it hard to do rolls. I sliced my thumb open trying to open a jar of peanut butter. Don&amp;rsquo;t ask. Not my proudest moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still working on the site(s). It&amp;rsquo;s still fun. But I&amp;rsquo;m running out of time. Life is speeding up and I&amp;rsquo;m struggling to keep pace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright. I&amp;rsquo;m done here. Peace out. I&amp;rsquo;ll get back to writing here someday, maybe, I don&amp;rsquo;t know.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Eyes Hurt</title>
      <link>https://blog.raidsrc.me/posts/my-eyes-hurt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:57:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.raidsrc.me/posts/my-eyes-hurt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Been coding nonstop this weekend. I&amp;rsquo;ve been making big progress on the site, and that&amp;rsquo;s been fun. But damn do my eyes hurt. Been staring at this screen for hours on end. I need to take a break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know, it sucks how the world is shifting towards a more digital, device-oriented society. We&amp;rsquo;ve always got technology in our faces. Always looking at stuff close-up. Ever since childhood. Staring at a screen consistently as a child sets you up for myopia in the future, since you&amp;rsquo;re probably not spending time outside in the sun and getting that vital dose of sunlight that&amp;rsquo;s necessary to signal your brain to release dopamine into your eyeballs for proper eye development in early life. At least that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten from the research I&amp;rsquo;ve read. It fucks our vision up, and that&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate. Well, as much as technology is responsible for our worsening vision, at least we have technology to thank for corrective lenses and laser eye surgery too. Not long ago, if your vision was bad, that was that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok. That&amp;rsquo;s it. Time to take a break.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another One</title>
      <link>https://blog.raidsrc.me/posts/another-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 13:35:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.raidsrc.me/posts/another-one/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Still building my website. It&amp;rsquo;s taking forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the University of California Davis, classes have been moved online until the end of January. I went back home to Piedmont and have decided to chill there for the time being. On one hand, I&amp;rsquo;ll have my basic needs met. Don&amp;rsquo;t need to worry about freezing my ass off when I wake up. Or starving to death. Plus I&amp;rsquo;ve got access to my upright piano and drum kit once more. Which is great. But on the other hand, I hate taking classes online. I fucking hate Zoom University. Remote learning is absolute garbage. Can&amp;rsquo;t focus, can&amp;rsquo;t motivate myself, can&amp;rsquo;t see the purpose of it, can&amp;rsquo;t do well. And I&amp;rsquo;ve got a little bit less freedom back home. Up at Davis I can do almost whatever I want, whenever I want. Just isn&amp;rsquo;t the same at home.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Good</title>
      <link>https://blog.raidsrc.me/posts/whats-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 12:38:04 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.raidsrc.me/posts/whats-good/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;abcd&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;abcd&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;asdfasdfasdfasdf&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;sup&#34;&gt;sup&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sup-1&#34;&gt;sup&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sup-2&#34;&gt;sup&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;b&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;c&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static void main(String[] args) {
  System.out.println(&amp;quot;yo&amp;quot;);
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://blog.raidsrc.me/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 09:52:56 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.raidsrc.me/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Testing testing testing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a hugo master&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not really&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;gohugo.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
